TU LIANG

JUNIOR UX/UI DESIGNER MONTREAL, CANADA

PERSONAL PROFILE

Passionate UX Designer, skilled in UX research and Sketch. Have strengths in creating pleasing UX experience, wireframing and prototyping. Have completed several projects, including an educational game for a museum and a delivery web app.

© 514-996-3520

□ lu.liang.ll18@gmail.com

https://lul18.github.io/LuLiang.github.io

JOB EXPERIENCE

Junior UX/UI Designer

(09. 2018 - PRESENT)

- Facilitated the design implementation of a delivery website via CSS and HTML coding;
- Translated prototypes and wireframes into a beautiful and easy-to-use artistic app:
- Created educational app for Inner Mongolia Museum for promoting an exhibition;
- Carried out user research through targeted interviews and extensive usability testing before and after the design;
- Completed courses on UX/UI design.

QA Tester

POLE TO WIN INTERNATIONAL, (06. 2020 - PRESENT)

- Find small bugs by doing testing, communicate with the manager and team members, and write reports;
- Understanding customer's needs and offer suggestions for fixing bugs;
- Assist and coordinate with the development team and other departments to make improvements.

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Concordia University, Montreal, Quebec

MASTER OF FINE ARTS, ART EDUCATION, 2018-2021

GPA: 3.85/4.0

Relevant Coursework:

- Research Practice: research design; data analysis, reports written;
- Foundations for Inquiry: Data analysis, Group work;
- Advanced Critical Analysis: Critical thinking, Brainstorm.
- Research Assistant (3 month)

Shandong University of Art & Design, Shandong, China BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS, DESIGN & ART HISTORY, 2013-2017

GPA:3.8/4.0

Relevant Experience: Research Assistant (2014-2015)

- Summarize interviews;
- Collected and analyzed data and managed the databases;
- Summarized project results.

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

Language

• Other Design Tools

Sketch
Figma
Invision
Procreate

Coding Language

HTML5

CSS3

C++

Python

• Adobe Creative Suite

Photoshop
Illustrator
Premiere Pro
After Effect

SOFT SKILLS

- Interpersonal skills
- Collaboration
- Communication
- Creative Thinking
- Detail Oriented
- Problem Solving
- Critical Thinking